type QuestionData = {
    question: string,
    options: string[],
    correct_option: number
}

export const questions: QuestionData[] = [
    {
        "question": "In which city does Batman fight crime?",
        "options": ["Metropolis", "Gotham", "Star City", "Central City"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Batman's real name?",
        "options": ["Clark Kent", "Bruce Wayne", "Oliver Queen", "Barry Allen"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Batman's loyal butler?",
        "options": ["Jarvis", "Lucius", "Pennyworth", "Alfred"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Batman's sidekick?",
        "options": ["Nightwing", "Robin", "Batgirl", "Red Hood"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Batmobile?",
        "options": ["A plane", "A motorcycle", "A car", "A boat"],
        "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which villain is known as the Clown Prince of Crime?",
        "options": ["Riddler", "Two-Face", "Penguin", "Joker"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Batman's cave?",
        "options": ["Wayne Cave", "Hero Hideout", "Batcave", "Gotham Lair"],
        "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which villain is obsessed with riddles?",
        "options": ["Joker", "Riddler", "Scarecrow", "Bane"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the CEO of Wayne Enterprises?",
        "options": ["Lucius Fox", "Bruce Wayne", "Alfred", "Harvey Dent"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Batman use to summon his allies?",
        "options": ["Bat-Radio", "Bat-Signal", "Bat-Phone", "Bat-Laser"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which villain broke Batman's back?",
        "options": ["Scarecrow", "Joker", "Two-Face", "Bane"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Batman's primary mission?",
        "options": ["To gain wealth", "To fight crime", "To become famous", "To conquer Gotham"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who killed Bruce Wayne's parents?",
        "options": ["Joker", "Joe Chill", "Two-Face", "Penguin"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Batman's utility belt contain?",
        "options": ["Gold", "Rocks", "Documents", "Gadgets"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Batman's Batplane?",
        "options": ["Batplane", "Wayne Jet", "Gotham Glider", "Batwing"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which villain is known for his split personality?",
        "options": ["Joker", "Bane", "Scarecrow", "Two-Face"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Batman's son?",
        "options": ["Jason Todd", "Dick Grayson", "Tim Drake", "Damian Wayne"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which group of heroes is Batman a founding member of?",
        "options": ["Teen Titans", "Justice League", "Suicide Squad", "Outsiders"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the Scarecrow use as his weapon?",
        "options": ["Bats", "Electricity", "Knives", "Fear gas"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the district attorney who becomes Two-Face?",
        "options": ["Edward Nygma", "Lucius Fox", "Harvey Dent", "Jim Gordon"],
        "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created Batman?",
        "options": ["Stan Lee", "Jack Kirby", "Joe Shuster", "Bob Kane and Bill Finger"],
        "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Poison Ivy's main power?",
        "options": ["Super strength", "Control over plants", "Hypnosis", "Invisibility"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which villain uses umbrellas as weapons?",
        "options": ["Riddler", "Joker", "Penguin", "Two-Face"],
        "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the leader of the League of Shadows?",
        "options": ["Talia al Ghul", "Ra's al Ghul", "Bane", "Joker"],
        "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What material is Batman's suit primarily made of?",
        "options": ["Steel", "Leather", "Kevlar", "Rubber"],
        "correct_option": 2
    }
];
